Guide to the Robert L. Bracklow Photograph Collection 1882-1918 (bulk, 1896-1905) PR 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Alland Purchase, 1
  - Subseries I.1: Alland Purchase: Negatives, 2
    - Teacher's College, 120th St. & Boulevard (another view) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1063)
    - Bryant Bldg., Liberty St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1064)
    - 94th St. [Old house] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1065)
    - Washington Bridge, 1889 [Washington Bridge (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1066)
    - Washington Bridge [Washington Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1066)
    - 6th Ave. & 11th St. [Old Grapevine Tavern] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1067)
    - [Old house and Steam Ship Hotel], West Broadway below Washington Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1068)
    - Nassau St. from John St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1069)
    - Marble Hill Ave. [church on corner] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1916 (Item 1070)
    - [Marble Hill Ave., showing river, bridge and elevated] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1916 (Item 1070)
    - [Marble Hill Ave., ball diamond below, elevated beyond] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1916 (Item 1070)
    - [63 Prince St., showing Vienna & Hungarian Café and Restaurant, G. Rosenber?] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1071)
    - [Germania Fire Insurance Co. Bldg., 1909] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1072)
    - 122-124 William St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1073)
      This image also appears in Album 11, page 16
    - Up Bronx River, 1891 [Ruins of mill in distance] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1074)
    - Fifth Ave. from 47th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1075)
    - 1-11 West 47th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1076)
    - Twenty-second Regiment leaving old armory, April 19, 1913 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1077)
    - Giant tulip tree, Inwood [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1078)
    - Claremont House, Riverside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1079)
    - Up Broadway [showing Trinity Church] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1080)
    - Grant Day reviewing stand [Riverside Drive, near Grant's Tomb] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1081)
    - [The Little Theatre] [] (Item 1082)
    - Weehawken Street, between Christopher Street and 10th Street, looking north [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1083)
    - Weehawken Street, looking south [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1083)
    - 86th St. near Riverside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1084)
    - Engine House, Centre St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1085)
      This image also appears in Album 4, page 15
    - [Alexander Lyman Holley statue] [], 1900 (Item 1086)
    - [New York skyline from the piers], 1915 [South St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1087)
    - [New York skyline from the piers, similar, including Seamen's Church Institute] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1915 (Item 1087)
    - [Looking north up Maiden Lane from South St., Tucker & Carter Rope Co. on corner, 1915] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1087)
    - Supreme Court, Appellate Division [25th St. & Madison Sq.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1088)
      This image also appears in Album 8, page 14
    - Another view of [Supreme Court, Appellate Division [25th St. & Madison Sq.], 1902 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1088)
    - Grand Boulevard north from 56th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 1089)
    - The Elephant Hotel, Coney Island [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 1090)
    - Seventh Ave. & [15th?] St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1091)
    - Astor House, 1902 & St. Paul's Chapel [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1092)
      This image also appears in Album 4, page 19
    - [John Anderson & Co., tobacconist, 114-116 ? St. Figure of Sir Walter Raleigh with pipe over door] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1093)
    - Herald Bldg., Herald Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1094)
      This image also appears in Album 2, page 79
    - Herald Bldg., Herald Square (another view) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1094)
      This image also appears in Album 2, page 78
    - [Harlem River, NYU on hill in distance] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1914 (Item 1095)
    - [Harlem River, Washington Bridge, Water Tower], 1914 [Washington Bridge (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1095)
    - Soldiers & Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive, under construction [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], [1900] (Item 1096)
    - Friends School, 15th St. & Stuyvesant Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1097)
    - Van Buren Estate, 14th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1910 (Item 1098)
    - Oscar G. Hickstein [or Meyers] Pharmacy, corner of [?] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1099)
      This image also appears in Album 4, page 4
    - Germania Theatre, Astor Place [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Item 1100)
    - Jumel Mansion [from below] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1101)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 24
    - Jumel Mansion, from below but nearer than No. 1101 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1101)
    - J. A. Morrison & Bldg., 23 Wall St., cor. Broadway, Drexel Bldg. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1102)
    - St. Luke's Church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 1103)
    - [Town on Hudson, church in foreground] [Perhaps at Spuyten Duyvil?] [] (Item 1104)
    - [Milestone: 8 Miles / 3 Quarters Brockland Ferry] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1105)
    - [Thomas Paine statue, New Rochelle, N.Y.] [New Rochelle (N.Y.)] (Item 1106)
    - [Thomas Paine Statue, New Rochelle, N.Y.], different printing [New Rochelle (N.Y.)] (Item 1106)
    - [Buggy on rutted street, men on sidewalk] [] (Item 1107)
    - [City Hall Park], 1898 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1108)
    - [Lafayette Statue] [] (Item 1109)
    - [Old Waldorf Astoria Hotel, Fifth Ave.] & Stuart house & Century Asso. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1110)
      This image also appears in Album 8, page 27
    - [Old houses, 78 W. 11th St. (6 Ave. elevated above) A. T. Leitiser, tailor [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1111)
    - [Abraham de Peyster statue, Bowling Green, erected 1896], 1898 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1112)
    - [William R. Boyce & Co. Bldg. with monument on wall, bldg. burned 1835, rebuilt 1836] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1113)
    - First Judicial District Court [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1114)
    - City College, 23rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1115)
    - Naval Parade, observed from rooftops [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1116)
    - Morningside & 120th St. [Squatter Shacks] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1117)
    - Naval Parade, Hudson River [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1118)
    - Wm. H. Seward Statue [Seward Park, 23rd Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1119)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 4
    - Cornelia St. from West 4th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1120)
      This image also appears in Album 14, page 18
    - City Hall, 1914 [Close up with Nathan Hale statue] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1121)
    - Greenwood Cemetary [monument] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1122)
    - Greenwood Cemetary [Elias Howe, Jr. monument] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1122)
    - Greenwood Cemetary [Dewey and other monuments] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1122)
    - Barnard College, 1897 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1123)
    - Maiden Lane & William St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1124)
    - National Park Bank Bldg. [Broadway and Fulton St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1125)
    - 8th Ave. & 86th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1126)
    - Grant's Tomb & Claremont House, Riverside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1127)
      This image also appears in Album 9, 11
    - Woman's Hospital [50th Street and Park Avenue] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1128)
    - Hof-Bräu Haus and Shanley's Restaurant [Third Avenue and 18th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1129)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 109
    - [Tower Bldg. and "The Washington" restaurant] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1130)
    - 473 Tenth Ave., 1895 [Also 469, 471 and 475] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1131)
    - Hotel Albemarle, 1903 [] (Item 1132)
    - Higgins House, 1894 [Old residence adjoining D. J. McCarthy, Carpenter, Lafayette St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1133)
    - [Collegiate Marble Church, with street decorated for Spanish American War naval celebration, '99], [28th St. & 5th Ave., Holland House at right] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1134)
    - [Observation tower in Park], Fire Tower, Mt. Morris Park, Madison Ave. & c.a.120th St] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1135)
    - Portuguese Synagogue [], 1899 (Item 1136)
    - Home for the Relief of the Destitute Blind, 104-106 Sts. & Boulevard [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1137)
    - Bronx River under the dam [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1138)
    - Varick St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1139)
    - [Hammerslough Brothers, Clothiers Bldg., next to cemetery, with removal notice, 109 Bleecker St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1140)
    - [Waldorf Astoria], looking down Fifth Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Item 1141)
    - [Waldorf Astoria] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Item 1141)
    - [Goldsmith Brothers store and, upstairs, Michael Woolf, optician, with removal signs, 77 Nassau St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1905 (Item 1142)
    - Wall St., 1917 [Redmond, Kerr & Co. and others draped in black and half masted flags] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1143)
    - Hotel St. George, 1900 [and adjoining street corner, 49 E. 12th St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1144)
    - National Bank of Commerce entrance [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1145)
    - [Corner of Maiden Lane and Water Sts., 1917?] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1146)
    - National Bank of Commerce entrance, close up [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1904 (Item 1147)
    - [Street scene with 2 old houses] [] (Item 1148)
    - Hotel Martha Washington, 1903 (the tall bldg.) [Madison Ave. and 30th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1149)
    - 56 Wall St., 1913 [Tablet to Moses Robinson by door. Kidder Peabody & Co.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1150)
    - [Woolworth Tower, 1913 from Barclay St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1151)
    - [Woolworth Tower, 1913 from Barclay St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1151)
    - Site of the Metropolitan Hotel [Old house] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1152)
    - Park Avenue Hotel [across the roofs] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1153)
    - [Plaque on modern Kings Bridge commemorating original bridge on same site] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1154)
    - Broadway & 73rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1155)
    - Evening Post Bldg. with decoration for 100th anniversary [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Item 1156)
    - [Crowds on roofs for naval parade, 1899] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1157)
      This image also appears in Album 5, page 11
    - Maiden Lane East of William St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1158)
    - St. Peter's Church, 20th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1159)
    - Hotel Marie Antoinette [Broadway and 67th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1160)
    - Twenty-second Regiment Armory [Broadway and 67th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1161)
    - [Corner of Broadway & Duane St., George and Harry's English Chop House, M. J. Adrian, cigars, Schoverling, Daly & Gales, guns, 302 Broadway] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1162)
    - From Astor Hotel window, 1907. [Madison Square Garden in right distance] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1163)
    - Juvenile Asylum [St. Nicholas Ave.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1164)
    - St. George Church, 16th St. [and Stuyvesant Sq.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1905 (Item 1165)
    - [Washington Square with arch in distance, looking north, 1916] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1166)
    - [North west side Washington Square from arch, 1916] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1167)
    - [Studio on Washington Mews] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1916 (Item 1168)
    - [Pennsylvania Station from 31st St., 1915] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1169)
    - [City Hall, 1899] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1170)
    - [Corn Exchange Bank entrance, corner William St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1171)
    - [Corbin Bldg., erected 1888, entrance; John St., near Broadway] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1172)
    - [Broadway, looking north past Trinity Church] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1173)
    - [Obelisk in Central Park] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1174)
    - [Woolworth Tower seen through arch of Municipal Bldg.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1175)
    - [Columbus statue, Columbus Circle, 1912] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1176)
    - [Monument on site of "American redout, 1776. Fort Washington Chapter D.A.R. 1910"] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1177)
    - [Large house with fenced yard] [], 1901 (Item 1178)
      This image also appears in Album 15, page 10
    - [Union Theological Seminary, Broadway and 120th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1179)
    - [St. Andrew's Roman Catholic Church, E. M. Lupton printing bldg. in rear, Duane Street and City Hall Place] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1180)
    - [House with ornate porch on Washington Square West] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1181)
    - [Church] [] (Item 1182)
    - [Mill and mill stream] [] (Item 1183)
    - [Two old houses back from street] [] (Item 1184)
    - [Union Theological Seminary, 120th Street and Broadway] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1185)
    - Hamilton Fountain, Riverside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1186)
    - [Battleships in Hudson, Hudson-Fulton Celebration, 1909] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1187)
    - Hotel Astor decorated for Hudson-Fulton Celebration [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1188)
    - [The College of the City of New York, through entrance arch] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1189)
    - [The College of the City of New York] another view] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1189)
    - [The College of the City of New York] another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1189)
    - [Plaque on building giving history of Liberty Place] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1190)
    - [Ruined mill by dam and waterfall] [] (Item 1191)
      This image also appears in Album 27, page 7
    - [Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive, close up] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1192)
    - [Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive, distant view] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1192)
    - [Old Lowe Library, Columbia University, 1909] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1193)
    - [Broad St. between No. 44 (Wall St. Journal Bldg.) and No. 58] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1194)
    - [Broad St. looking north from Beaver St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1195)
    - [Fleet in Hudson, 1911] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1196)
    - [Battleship in Hudson, 1911] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1196)
    - [Looking south on Centre St. from New York Dispensary to Tombs prison] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1197)
    - [Royal Insurance Co. Bldg. with service flag, World War I., c. a. 1918] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1198)
    - [Looking west on Wall St. to Trinity. Flags at half mast] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1199)
    - Greeley Statue, 1896 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1200)
      This image also appears in Album 2, page 80
    - [Haeger's Storage Warehouse, corner west 33rd St. and Eighth Avenue] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1915 (Item 1201)
    - [Haeger's Storage Warehouse, from 34th St., new Post Office beyond] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1915 (Item 1201)
    - [Old entrance with lions and doric columns. S. Carey, Millstones and bolting cloths, 17 Broadway, 1896] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1202)
    - [Two business bldgs. Robert L. Bracklow (the photographer), stationer, No. 101 Maiden Lane; Anchor Packing Co., No. 103] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1916 (Item 1203)
    - [Single story stone wall with 5 doors, one bricked up] [] (Item 1204)
    - [Metropolitan Life Tower] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1205)
    - [Metropolitan Life Tower], another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1205)
    - [Battleship in Hudson] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], [1896] (Item 1206)
    - [Another Battleship in Hudson] The "New York"? [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], [1896] (Item 1206)
    - [View from Broadway across Trinity Churchyard to Trinity Building on north side] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1207)
      This image also appears in Album 4, page 23
    - [End view of (Trinity) building, looking across Broadway to west] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1207)
      This image also appears in Album 4, page 22
    - Bronx Park and mill (Lorrilard Snuff Mill) [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1208)
    - Bronx police booth, cop and horse [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1209)
    - Bronx Church House Camp [Tents] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1210)
    - Bronx Church House Camp. [Group of boys with tents in background] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1210)
    - 16-22 John St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1211)
    - [St. Luke's Hospital], 113th St. looking east, old house on site at the Cathedral [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1212)
    - [Entrance of Anchor Line office entrance, 17 Broadway, with doric columns and lions, 1912] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1213)
    - [Store of R. G. Hutchinson, stationers, No. 18 John St., 1902] (shutters up) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1214)
    - [Store of R. G. Hutchinson, stationers, with shutters of adjacent stores down] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], [1902] (Item 1214)
    - Hague St. "Hogan's Alley?" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1215)
    - [Lowe Library, Columbia University, 1898] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1216)
    - [Old Lowe Library, Columbia University, 1898] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1216)
    - [New Post Office] Eighth Avenue from 34th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1915 (Item 1217)
    - New Post Office, Eighth Avenue from 33rd Street, 1915 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1217)
    - Milestone: "12 miles from N. York" [], 1912 (Item 1218)
    - Milestone: "15 miles from New York" [], 1912 (Item 1219)
    - [Business block draped in bunting for Hudson Fulton Celebration, 1909], Drexel, Morgan Bldgs., 23 Wall St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1220)
    - [Interior of stationer's store with Hudson Fulton decorations, 1909] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1220)
    - U.S.S. Indiana in Hudson for Hudson-Fulton Celebration, 1909 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1221)
    - H.M.S. Invincible, in Hudson for Hudson-Fulton Celebration, 1909 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1221)
    - [Across roof tops to Waldorf Astoria Hotel from Wst 31st St., 1905][Looking north] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1222)
    - [Across roof tops to Waldorf Astoria Hotel from west 31st St., 1905], [looking north] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1222)
    - [Road, trees and snow in Central Park] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1223)
    - Whitehall Bldg. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1224)
    - Custom House, 1913 [Detail of steps, looking east] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1225)
    - Custom House, looking west [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1225)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive, 1903 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1226)
    - [Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive, 1903] another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1226)
    - [Old house in large fenced yard at] Amsterdam Ave. & 115th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1227)
    - [Old houses and stores, corner of ?, B. Wasserman, cigars; N.Y. Law Journal, 1902] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1228)
    - [Lane off John St., at corner occupied by H. A. Rogers, 19 John St., 1899] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1229)
    - 8th Ave. & 43rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1230)
    - [Entrance to City Investing Bldg., City Investing Co., National Reserve Bank, No. 165 Broadway] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1231)
    - 17 John St. [former site of store of J. M. Thorburn & Co., seedmen, removed to 36 Cortland St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1232)
    - American Geographical Society [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1233)
    - 19 West 34th St. [Old mansion] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1234)
      This image also appears in Album 8, page 19
    - Bronze placque on site of sugar house, below barred window from original sugar house. This building erected in 1895 on site of Rhinelander Sugar House built in 1765… [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1235)
    - Metropolitan Opera House, 1896 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1236)
      This image also appears in Album 2, page 77
    - Riverside Drive & 111th St.[Old house] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1237)
    - Riverside Drive & 83rd St. [6 story bldg. under construction, with sign advertising windows for sale for Grant Parade, seats $3.00 each] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1238)
    - Hudson River Railroad station at 30th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1239)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 2
    - Maiden Lane & Front St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1240)
    - [Maiden Lane & Front St., another view, Schering and Glatz bldg.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1240)
    - [Washington Hotel?; 1 Broadway, Nicholas Muller, ticket agency. Bronze plaque on wall stating that this was site of house occupied by Generals Washington and Lee] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1241)
    - Edgar Allen Poe House, Fordham, 1911 [on original site before removal to Poe Park] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1242)
    - Poe Statue, 1911 [] (Item 1242)
    - Fifth Ave. from 48th St. West from Madison Ave. showing Collegiate Reformed Church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1243)
      This image also appears in Album 11, page 14
    - [Lower sky line of New York from Brooklyn, World bldg. to Trinity] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1244)
      This image also appears in Album 7, page 18
    - Nathan Hale statue, City Hall in background, 1912 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1245)
    - Home for the Relief of the Destitute Blind [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1246)
    - Central Park West & 70th St.? [Shack] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1247)
    - [Fifth Ave., 40th to 42nd Sts., with billboards around site of removed Reservoir] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1248)
      This image also appears in Album 7, page 11
    - Broadway & 50th St. [Old bldgs.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1249)
    - Knickerbocker Trust Co. bldg. [Fifth Avenue and 34th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1905 (Item 1250)
    - Peter Cooper Homestead Restaurant, 28th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1251)
    - Milestone: "2 miles from City Hall" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1252)
    - Hudson River from Fort Washington [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1889 (Item 1253)
    - Broadway from 30th St. [Daly's Theatre] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1254)
      This image also appears in Album 8, page 17